This Is Not A Sequel. There Has Never Been Anything Like It!
Beyond the Valley of the Dolls is a comedy, drama,
music film directed by Russ Meyer.
An all-girl rock band moves to Hollywood in the hope of achieving success,
only to fall into a whirlpool of wickedness and decadence.
Kelly McNamara, played by Dolly Read.
Casey Anderson, played by Cynthia Myers.
Petronella Danforth, played by Marcia McBroom.
Ronnie Z-Man Barzell, played by John Lazar.
Lance Rocke, played by Michael Blodgett.
Harris Allsworth, played by David Gurian.
Beyond the Valley of the Dolls is a 1970 American satirical musical melodrama film starring Dolly Read, Cynthia
Myers, Marcia McBroom, Phyllis Davis, John LaZar, Michael Blodgett, Erica Gavin, and David Gurian.
The film was directed by Russ Meyer and written by Roger
Ebert from a story by Ebert and Meyer.
Originally intended as a direct sequel to the 1967 film Valley of the Dolls, Beyond the
Valley of the Dolls was instead revised as a satirical extension of the original.
Beyond was met with negative reviews upon its initial
release, but it became a box office success.
The film developed a cult following in subsequent decades and has since earned
critical reappraisal for its satirical and metafictional elements.
The film explores themes of pop star, pop, musical, sexploitation, rock band.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.